A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Map of Itmann Mine workings, Beckley Seam, undated (Box 237)
  - Aerial Photographs: 863: 176-200 (Box 237)
  - Aerial Photographs: 863: 151-175 (Box 237)
  - Aerial Photographs: 863: 201-225 (Box 237)
  - Aerial Photographs: 863: 226-250 (Box 237)
  - Geologic Cross Section of Drillholes 4,5,52,53,54 (Box 237)
  - S & C Coal Company No. 8 Mine, Mullens, West Virginia. (Box 237)
  - Topographic map of unidentified area. (Box 237)
  - Description of Tract No. 3. (Box 237)
  - [Aerial Photographs] #s 1296 thru 1809, location unknown, 41 photographs (Box 238)
  - [Aerial Photographs] #s 1296 thru 1809, location unknown, 60 photographs total (Box 238)
  - Justice Dam G.P. and U.S.A. 1"=2000' 269 (Box 239)
  - Three Forks Topographical Maps 1981 1"=100', 1981 (Box 240)
  - Track Maps (Box 241)
  - Bishop #33 Tipple (Box 242)
  - Jacob's Fork Subdivision (Box 243)
  - Right of Way and Track Map Virginia & Western R.R. Co.'s (Box 244)
  - Collieries, Acreage, and Tonnage (Box 245)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1937/05 (Box 246)
  - Lease Property Boundaries, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Wyoming County, West Virginia (Box 247)
  - Property Maps - West Virginia (Box 248)
  - Lost Ridge Topographical Maps 1979 1"=100', 1979 (Box 249)
  - Jacob's Fork and Tributaries (Box 250)
  - Seam No. 3 Maps (Box 251)
  - Consolidated Coal Company RookHouse Ridge Tracings (Box 252)
  - Lost Ridge Topographical Maps 1977 & 1978 1"=100', 1977-1978 (Box 253)
  - Three Forks Aerial Topographical Maps 1" = 200' (Originals) (Box 254)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps 1977 & 1978 1"=100', 1977-1978 (Box 255)
  - 176. Sugar Run (Box 256)
  - 194. Silver Ridge (Box 257)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps 1982 1"=200', 1982 (Box 258)
  - Lost Ridge Topographical Maps 1980 1"=100', 1980 (Box 259)
  - Tracings Statements of Holdings of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. and Subsidiaries, 123, 1925/12/31 (Box 260)
  - 286. Buckeye No. 3 Seam Profiles; Profile Buckeye No. 4 Mines drafts and data (Box 261)
  - Three Forks Topographical Maps 1982 & Final 1"=100', 1982 (Box 262)
  - Maps Showing Land of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. and Consol Coal Co. Land areas & mine areas (Box 263)
  - 149. Itmann Bridge; 60-79 (Box 264)
  - Bandy Mains Profiles (Box 265)
  - Pocahontas Filtration Plant (Box 266)
  - Test Holes (Box 267)
  - 249. C.R.P. 56 to 60 Charts Poca-Bishop-Cr.Ck & Itmann (Box 268)
  - 1"=1000' Contour Tracings Itmann & Deerfield 298.; Topographical Maps Itmann, Deerfield (Box 269)
  - 202. N.&W. Pineville to Marianna; Marianna Right of Way (Box 270)
  - Beaver Creek Coal Company Floyd & Knott Co. Kentucky 1"=2000' (Box 271)
  - Bishop Property Maps (Box 272)
  - Highways of Appalachia (Box 273)
  - Track Plans (Box 274)
  - 201. Tracings Boiss Shafts and Slopes; Shafts & Slop Plans cross-sections (Box 275)
  - 132. Old Power Charts to 1949 (Box 276)
  - Shawnee Mountain Topographical Maps 1983 1"=200', 1983 (Box 277)
  - 201. N&W Right of Way Amonate, Bishop, Jenkin Jones, Crane-Creek, Piedmont, Pulaski, Covel; Road Bluelines (Box 278)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps 1979 1"=100'; Consol Rockhouse Topographical Maps, 1979 (Box 279)
  - Std. Surface Mine Maps; Consol Surface Mine Maps (just area) (Box 280)
  - Maps Wyoming Co. Property Itmann Mine & Reserves ISO Contours Bore Holes Channel Sections 71.; Bore Holes (Box 281)
  - 131. Old All Colleries. Power Charts 1913 to-; Colliery Reports (Box 282)
  - Maps Tracings W.M. Ritter Bore holds Profiles Tracings 36.; Maps Showing leased land to Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Guyandotte River Wyoming County, West Virginia Near Pineville R.M. Ritter lease Outcrop of coal seams on Itmann Leasehold (Box 283)
  - Boone County Maps (Box 284)
  - Matthews Mines #1, #2, #3 Mine Map (Orig.) 1"=300'; Various Drawings (Box 285)
  - Redfox Jr. Pocahontas Stripping (Box 286)
  - 114. House Prints Lots Purchase By J.H. Lilly Land Company Covel, Piedmont, Pinnacle, Sagamore, and Pulaski Keep for Record 1"=50' 11-4-57 (Box 287)
  - Bearhold Road 46.; Wyoming County West Virginia Road Construction (Box 288)
  - 129. Proposed Belt Extension Bishop; Topographical Maps; Jim Flannigan Horsepen (Box 289)
  - 135. Profiles Inside No. 2 (Box 290)
  - Pocahontas Reclaim Area (Box 291)
  - Pocahontas-Consol Annual Reports, 1904-1944 (Box 292)
  - 112 Tracings of Parcels at Covel, Sagamore, Piedmont, Pinnacle and Pulaski Scale 1"=100' 11-4-57;Sagamore, Shawnee, Pulaski (Box 293)
  - Maps Showing Still Run area (Box 294)
  - Bishop Upper Seams 1"=1000' Maps Showing Deep Mine Reserves H.P. to Jacobs Fork 182.; Maps showing multiple seams in the same area (Box 295)
  - Tracings Base 1"=1000' A.M.S. 255.; Topographical Maps Showing Different Seams (Box 296)
  - Map Showing Consol Lands and Mine Boundaries (Box 297)
  - BU.-2 Topographical Tracings Various Scales Buch. Co, 186.; Buchanan County Topographical Maps (Box 298)
  - 160-179 Virginia - No Mines (Box 299)
  - Ritter Lands Maps of Proposed Leases Nos. 1-2-3-6 Scale 1"=500' 34.;Wyoming Co. W.M. Ritter Lumber (Box 300)
  - 238. Tracings Sagamore No. 11 Seam 1"=200' (Box 301)
  - 172. Tracings Fans (Box 302)
  - Guyandotte Bore Holes (Box 303)
  - Cabin Creek Negatives (Box 304)
  - Maps Showing Area of Matthews Mine - Consol Coal No Mine Workings (Box 305)
  - Shawnee Mountain Topographical Maps 1981 1"=100', 1981 (Box 306)
  - Area around Eckman-Page Mines; Eckman Area Topographical Maps (Box 307)
  - Consol - South Appalachian Region West Virginia (Box 308)
  - Reed Topographical Maps 1977 & 1978 1"=100' (final), 1977-1978 (Box 309)
  - 148. Itmann Lease hold & V.G.N. R.O.W. Maps; Itmann Properties (Box 310)
  - Three Forks Topographical Maps 1978-1979 1"=100', 1978-1979 (Box 311)
  - No. 1 Wyoming Co. Coal Lands P.L. Corp. Tracings 23. 1"=300' Nos. 9321-9325 Nos. 9341-9345; Maps showing lease properties in West Virginia - Some Pocahontas land (Box 312)
  - 250 No. 12 & 13 Seams Nassau North Fork Tug (Box 313)
  - Amonate District Area Cross-Section (Box 314)
  - 206. Kentucky Block Fuel Company; Prints & Plans Kentucky Block (Box 315)
  - Red Fox Progress Mylar; Kentucky Quads (Box 316)
  - Old Horsepen, West Virginia Mine Maps (Box 317)
  - Pageton Original Topographical; Topographical maps of Pageton Slurry impoundment Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 318)
  - Bishop 400' Base Maps A.M.S. 102 (Box 319)
  - 234. Maps Upper Seams Saga.-Chero. & Angle Leaseholds; Pocahontas Corp. and U.S.C.&C. Co. lands Horsepen Cir area Coal Contour lines (Box 320)
  - N&W Rights Of Way Lick Branch, Maybeury and Rolfe. 204. (Box 321)
  - Cumberland Mountain Topographical Maps (Box 322)
  - Coal Fields near Gauley River (Box 323)
  - 332. Tracings Annual Reports, 1948-1957 (Box 324)
  - Misc. Mylars 230.; Topographical maps 7.5 min quads West Virginia/Virginia (Box 325)
  - Shawnee Mountain Topographical Maps 1979 & 1980 1"=100', 1978-1979 (Box 326)
  - Shawnee Mountain Topographical Maps 1984 1"=-200', 1984 (Box 327)
  - No. 2 Wyoming Co. Coal Lands P.L. Corp. Tracings 1"=300' Nos. 9361-9365 and Nos, 9383-9386 24.; Maps showing land ownership in Acres and bounding coordinates (Box 328)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps Current Year 1"=200' (Box 329)
  - 223. Horsepen Seam Laurel Creek 1'=500'; Topographical Maps Maps with Horsepen seam (Box 330)
  - Coal Bank Topographical Maps 1979 1"=100'; Consol Coal Co. Horsepen Virginia Coalbank Topographical Maps, 1979-1980 (Box 331)
  - Pocahontas Building Floor Plans Exploration-Engineering Move, 1984 (Box 332)
  - Lands of American Assoc. Inc. Bore Holes Tracings Scale: 1"=2000'; Topographical and Prop Maps Go with document OSM #700609 Claiborne County, TN (Box 333)
  - Ritter Lease Traverse & Area Sheets Main Boundary P.F.C. Inc. No. 3 Seam Lease 41.; Ritter Prop Survey (Box 334)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc.. Inc. Lease Properties Wyoming County (Box 335)
  - 296. 1960 AIME Meeting (Box 336)
  - Mary Lynn Coal Co. Maps; Maps of leased lands and boreholes Guyandotte River, Pineville coal seams (Box 337)
  - 32. BU. 24 Buch. Co. Topographical Maps 1"=500' (Box 338)
  - 44. Itmann Deerfield & Gooney-Otter Upper Seams 1"=400 with cover lines (Box 339)
  - 198. Tracings Store Buildings. 26. (Box 340)
  - Fatal Accidents from Different Mines (Box 341)
  - Tidewater Profiles (Box 342)
  - 147. BU-31 Buchanan Co. Coal Field Bore-hold Correlations Charts Analysis All Coals (Box 343)
  - 136. New Profiles inside No. 3 (Box 344)
  - 226. Maitland Ventilation Surveys (Box 345)
  - Pocahontas Borehole Map, Wyoming County (Box 346)
  - Shipped Tonnage Compiled by the Pocahontas Operators Association, 47, 1883-1953 (Box 347)
  - Buckeye Abandonment Plans; Topographical maps and plans for Stephenson Refuse area Consol Coal Co. (Box 348)
  - Tracings New Pocahontas High School 14.00 AC. TR. 1"=100=, 1"=50' (Box 349)
  - 194. Houses and Roads Itmann Collieries (Box 350)
  - Data Sheets for So. Fork #4 Seam 100-119 (Box 351)
  - 27. Photo Index Map Pocahontas Coal Field (Box 352)
  - 173. Maps Roseville and Bluestone; Homes along Laurel Creek (Box 353)
  - 147. Unleased Lands Adjoining Itmann Guyandotte (Box 354)
  - Miner 12 Sepias of 11-C.M. Joy Manufacturing Co. 163.; Buildings and wiring plans, no mine workings (Box 355)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps 1984 1"=200', 1984 (Box 356)
  - Section Analysis of middle and upper Horsepen Seam (Box 357)
  - 155. Bluefield Telephone Company (Box 358)
  - Topographical Maps Pineville Quad (Box 359)
  - 30. Wyoming Co. Leaseholds Diamond Core Drilling by Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Tracings Scale 1"=1000' (Box 360)
  - 133. New Power Charts 1949 to -- (Box 361)
  - Prop Maps Corresponds to OSM #700622 (Box 362)
  - McDowell Co. West Virginia Pageton Area (Box 363)
  - Shawnee Mountain Mining Maps 1"=200' (Box 364)
  - Maps Showing Multiple Seams Company Props Data Sheets (Box 365)
  - Skyline Prep Plant Topographical 1"=100'; Evanston, Ky. Area Topographical Maps (Box 366)
  - Three Forks Topographical Maps 1980 1"=100' All Topographical Maps, No Mine Maps, 1980 (Box 367)
  - 80. RT.-LHLD. No. 5 MS. = RS.-DH.-CTS.; Wyoming County Boreholes (Box 368)
  - United Producing Co. Wells W.M. Ritter Lumber Co. Lease Wyoming County, West Virginia (Box 369)
  - 10 yr. Progress Maps Shawnee Mountain Surface, Horsepen, West Virginia Surface, Redfox Surface, 1985-1986 (Box 370)
  - Map Showing Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Owned Land around Pineville (Box 371)
  - Bishop Mountain Top Aerial Topographical Maps 1"=200' (Originals) (Box 372)
  - Consolidation Coal Co. Southern Appalachia Region showing proposed Disturbed Area, 1984-1997 (Box 373)
  - Crozer Tipple Plans (Box 374)
  - Topographic Map of Bishop Colliery 1"=50' (Box 375)
  - Boreholes around Tackett Creek, TN (Box 376)
  - #12682-2 Consol Coal 1"=200' (Box 377)
  - Coal Bank Topographical Maps 1980 1"-100' (Final & Valley Fills), 1980 (Box 378)
  - Lost Ridge Topographical Maps 1981 1"-100'), 1981 (Box 379)
  - Heavy Media Wash Box Tracings 224 (Box 380)
  - BU-28 Buchanan Co. ISO-Tracings 1"=5000' Consol 156 (Box 381)
  - Rockhouse Topographical Maps 1981 1" = 100', 1981 (Box 382)
  - Buchanan Coal Field Consol 213 BU - 20 (C.) Seam 1"=5000' (Box 383)
  - Itmann, Deerfield, Gooney, Otter Base Maps for Outcrop and Reserves 1" - 1000' 25; A.M.S. Sewell & Beckley Seam Outcrops (Box 384)
  - Lost Ridge Topographical Maps 1982 1"=200', 1982 (Box 385)
  - 217 Lillybrook (Box 386)
  - Shawnee Mountain Topographical Maps 1982 1" = 200', 1982 (Box 387)
  - 96 Berwind Canebrake Hartwell Newhall Lots 1"=100' 1'=50' (Box 388)
  - 37 Seaboard Seam Topographical Maps (Box 389)
  - 197 Tracings - Schools and Churches 22; Boissevain School House, 1920 (Box 390)
  - All Collieries Active Mine Openings and Haulage Track, 156; Isopach, Sterling, Upper Mason, Hignite Seams, 1954 (Box 391)
  - Contour Tracings Amonate Scale 1"=100' 77; Topographical maps on Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. land (Box 392)
  - Contents: 7 Coal Height Isopach Maps (Lower Seams) 1 Contour Map Scale 1"=1000'; Topographical maps of Jenkin Jones area Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 393)
  - Itmann, Deerfield, & Gooney-Otter 400' Base Maps Enlarged from Toposheets 302 (Box 394)
  - Ritter Triangulation System Tracings and Maps Scale 1"=2000' 38; Ritter land maps (Box 395)
  - Accident Sketch Originals All Mines! 303 Cross sections and data - Consol Amonate 31 (Box 396)
  - 530 Right-of-Way & Track-Map N&W R.W. 1"=1000'; Maps showing lease properties Crozer Land Co. (Box 397)
  - Map of Slurry Pond Building, Roads, Tracks, etc. (Box 398)
  - McCreary & Leslie County Kentucky Maps 109; Structural & aerial geology McCreary & Leslie Co. KY (Box 399)
  - 172 Annual Reports 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74 (Box 400)
  - P-Entry Roof Fall 07-29-82 267; Amonate #31 Roof Failures (Box 401)
  - Itmann Topography & Outcrop 145; Itmann Topographical Maps & Leaseholds (Box 402)
  - JenkinJones Imp. Aerial Mapping Scale: 1"=100'; Topographical maps of Consol land Jenkin Jones Area McDowell Co., West Virginia (Box 403)
  - Turkey Gap Old Tracings 311 1"-100' Old Tracings Modoc & Wenonah 1"=100', OSM #700608 (Box 404)
    Scanned by VTSC (no CON#)
  - Tracings and Drawings for Lillybrook Coal Co., Other Coal Co.'s as well (Box 405)
  - Bu.-19 Topographical. Film Negatives 192; Virginia/West Virginia (Box 406)
  - Contour Maps Virginia/West Virginia (Box 407)
  - Topographical Maps - Berwind Property West Virginia (Box 408)
  - Topographical Maps Virginia/West Virginia border, McDowell/Tazewell Co. area of OSM #700582 (Box 409)
  - Wyoming Co. Iso. Contours (Box 410)
  - 111 Wyoming County Borehole Prospecting West of Baileysville 16-20 inc (Box 411)
  - No. 1 Wyoming County Coal Lands P.L.C. Maps Scale 1"=300' Nos. 9321-9323 Nos. 9341-9345 26.; Lease property boundaries in Wyoming County West Virginia (Box 412)
  - Maps Showing Contour Lines (elevation) Consol Coal Co. (Box 413)
  - Kepler Plastic Tracing Showing Gas Wells, Property Lines, etc. 1"=500'; Maps of Kepler Prop. No mine workings (Box 414)
  - Itmann Store and Office 144 (Box 415)
  - 378 Dr. Porter: Residence Plans for Dr. and Mrs. H. A. Porter, Pocahontas, Virginia, 9/3-10/1946 (5 sheets), 1946/09 (Box 416)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "All Collieries – Scales".]
  - A- Nut & Pea Screens, A- Nut & Pea Screens, Tipple Drawing, #32 Slack Bin, #32 Slack Bin, #32 Pea Bin, Bi – Dom. Coal Bin, #30 Fan old – [stage?] are [ovone?] (Box 416)
  - Bi - Washer, Bi- Tipple, Bi- Slack Layout, Bi- Washer Layout, P- Scale House, P- Rom Boom, P- Screens, S- Rom Chute, P- Screen Detail, P- Steel Delalts, P- Rom Drive, P- Rom Boom (Box 417)
  - #7- House Coal Ch., S- Dry Slack Slatt., S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Coal Chute, S- Dry Slack, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, S- Dry Slack Layout, B- Crusher, S- Dry Slack, S- Dry Slack (Box 417)
  - Joe M. Sayko Garage and Roller Skating Rink, Abbs Valley, Virginia (Box 418)
  - Gillespie Garage, Tazewell, Virginia (Box 418)
  - Power Distribution (1934), 0/0, Ash, Fusion-All col. #7 Oil System, F- Store, Bi-Slack Storage, Bi- Slack Storage, B.C. - Ref. Disposal, 1934 (Box 419)
  - #31 Machinery Layout, #31, Sand House and Office, B- Pump House Tower, B- Water Plant, B- Pump House, B- Pump House, #31 Pick Breaker, #31 Big Shaker, Bi. Larry Car, B0 Stove Boom, #31 Drive fr. Slack, Shannon Jig, #31 Pick Breaker, #31 Pick Breaker, #31 Pick Breaker, #7 Screens, B- Stove Boom (Box 419)
  - Link-Belt Chute, #31 – Masonry Abut, Dry Fork House La, #31 Tipple floor Plan, S- Tipple Wet Slack, D- [Crushep?], R – Head House, #31 – Clean up elev., #31 – Big Shaker, #31 – Tipple addition, #31 – Tipple addition (Box 420)
  - B – Perm. Stopping, Bi – Fan (Aero.), #31 – Tipple, Bi – Tank Supports, B – Stove Boom, S – Rom Chute, S – Big Shaker, S – Pea Bin, S - Pea Bin (plate), S – Pea Bin (plate), #31 – Dom. Bin, #31 – Tipple, #31 – Dom. Coal Bin, #33 – Coal Bin, S – Pea Bin (Box 420)
  - House Plans, J- #8 Lamp House, L.B. Com. Building, D- House Burned, PI – House Burned, Bi. Post Office, P- Est. House Burned, 5 room Rams, 3 room Plans, Bi. Mantle, F. Stone & Office, L.B. Com. Building., F. Store, F. Store, P. O. House seating, L. B. Com. Building., F. Store (roof), Bi. Store (Box 421)
  - S – Refuse Bin, S – Dry Slack, A – Nut & Pea Screens, S – Ref. Bin, S – Dry Slack, S – Dry Slack, S – Ref. Bin, ? Screens, S – Wet Screens, S- Wet Screens, L. B. Raw C. Screens, A – Nut & Pea Screens, A- Nut & Pea Screens, L. B. – Tipple, A. – [Nashed c.?] screens (Box 421)
  - #37 Bridge, F – Bridge (Highway), Bi. – Tipple layout, Bi – Bridge, Bi – Bridge (Ren. Concrete), Bi – Bridge (Ren. Concrete), #37 – Bridge, P – Bridge, Bi. – Tipple layout, Bi. – Tipple layout, F. – Bridge (Box 422)
  - #37 – Mine Office, S – Fan, Bi. Dp. Office, B – Crushep, F – Fan (Aero.), F – Fan (Aero.), #32 – Dump (Rot.), #32 – Dump (Rot.), #32 – Dump (Rot.) (Box 422)
  - A – Nut & Pea Screens, A – Screen Details, A – Screen Details, L.B., Screen (Raw coal), A. – Screen (Details), A – Screen Nut & Pea, A – Screen Nut & Pea, A – Screen Nut & Pea, L. B. – Screen (High speed), L. B. – Screen (Sec.) (Box 423)
  - No. 33 Team Road Profile, Nov. 2, 1951, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bishop, Virginia, Profile of No. 33 Mine Tram Road from [CL] of No. 33 Tipple Dump to No. 33 Drift Mouth; Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bishop, Virginia, Profile of No. 34 Mine Tram Road from [CL] of No. 33 Tipple Dump to No. 34 Drift Mouth, No. 34 Team Road Profile, Nov. 2, 1951; [Untitled drawings, drafts of No. 34 Team Road Profile, 11/2/1951?], 1951 (Box 424)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Larry Car, Bishop, Virginia, 1931/01/05 (Box 424)
  - Pulaski Lease, Coal Sections of Stripping, 1951/12/27 (Box 424)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Boissevain Stove Boom Details, 10/11/1935; The McNally Pittsburgh Manufacturing Corp., Existing Machinery Layout, Mine #31, Amonate, Virginia, for the Pocahontas Corporation, Pocahontas, Virginia., 6/4/1936, 1935/10/11, 1936/06/04 (Box 424)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bishop, Virginia, Profile of No. 33 and No. 34 Mine Tracks from [CL?] of No. 33 Tipple Dump to No. 33 and No. 34 Mines (Box 424)
  - #7 Jones (Box 424)
  - [Certificate] Jamestown Tercentennial Exposition on Hampton Roads, Virginia, 1907, Commemorating the First Permanent English Settlement in America[,] The Jury of Awards has conferred a Silver Medal upon State Crop Pest Commission, for Illustrations of its Work, 1907 (Box 425)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Itmann".]
  - Map of James Adair's Estate at Bell Point, Sept. 1895, print made 3/26/1930, 1930/03/26 (Box 425)
  - [Set of plans for Itmann #1 Mine tracks and profile], undated (Box 425)
  - [Photo of] Goodwill, Sagamore, Pinnacle, & Piedmont [with memo from Thomas J. Sawarynski to Lou Ostendorff about Crane Creek 12 Seam mine], 1982/01/13 (Box 426)
  - [Charts, maps, drawings, and photo of Bishop, Virginia area tipples, stations, etc.:] 32033 Phantom View of Link-Belt Multi-Louvre Dryer, May 1950; The V.G. Multiclone; Rotoclone "N" Dust Collector, [Drawing of machinery connected to furnace]; Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Diagrammatic Flow Sheet Bishop Cleaning Plant, Pocahontas, Virginia, 4/29/1955; [Map of Bishop, Virginia, area tipples, dust collecting stations, residences, etc.]; [Chart of wind directions near Bishop, Virginia, 1955-1956]; [Map of Bishop, Virginia, area tipples, stations, etc.]; [Composite aerial photo of Bishop, Virginia, area tipples, stations, etc.], 1950-1956 (Box 426)
  - Aerial photographs, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., [1945?] (Box 427)
  - 6 maps, Laurel Creek Upper Seam, Smith Seam, and other unidentified areas, 1968-1975 (Box 427)
  - Photos, Bath County, Virginia (Box 427)
  - [Various Maps:] Buckhorn Iron and Improvement Co. property, Russell and Buchanan Counties, Virginia; Johnston-Strader Tract and J. Raleigh Johnston Tract, Giles County, [Virginia?]; Banner Raven Coal Corporation, outcrop and mine workings, Upper Banner Seam, Drill, Virginia; Garden Coal Co. Inc., Drill, Russell County, Virginia; Longley Coal Corporation, Widow Kennedy Seam, Drill, Virginia; Bushkill Mine Map (Box 427)
  - Sections Along R.R. Track at Bent, Fine Coal Cleaning Plant for Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Amonate, Virginia, 1953/01/06 (Box 428)
  - West Virginia State Highway, McDowell County Line to Bramwell (Box 428)
  - Elkhorn Road, State of West Virginia State Road Commission, Plan and Profile of Proposed Construction of State Road 3007 Project, Elkhorn District, McDowell County from Mayberry to McDowell County Line (Box 428)
  - Itmann, Project Abandoned [?], 1976/03/05 (Box 429)
  - Info on Berwind Lease, memo to Jim McKenzie from Thomas J. Sawarynski, 1981/10/28 (Box 429)
  - Natural gas pipeline systems (Box 429)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Rolfe Leasehold [partial map] (Box 429)
  - Maps showing property and lease lines, corresponding with OSM #700565-700569, Killarney Tipple, Pocahontas No. 4 Seam, Beckley Seam Outcrop (Box 429)
  - Bishop Impoundment Clarification, Consolidation Coal Company, 1980 (Box 430)
  - Work done at 31 mains to K Mains, 1975-1976 (Box 430)
  - Lillybrook Coal Co., Power Dist. System, Transmission Lines, Property Lines, same area as OSM #700626 (Box 430)
  - Railroad and House, Killarney Smokeless Coal Co., Next to Stone Coal Creek (Box 430)
  - No Name Town [plat, possibly Crockett, West Virginia or Crockett, Virginia] (Box 430)
  - Tazewell Co., Virginia map, including Little Stone Ridge and Baptist Valley (Box 430)
  - Peerless Dump Layout, 1956/11/06 (Box 431)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Delta - Lick Branch / Bottom Creek – Peerless - Eckman".]
  - Peerless Colliery plans, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. of Consolidation Coal Company, Vivian, West Virginia, 1959/01/24 (Box 431)
  - Head Pulley (Box 431)
  - No Mine Workings, Bishop Compressor Foundation, Union Hall, [Froth Cell?] Bearings and Paddles for Skinner Assembly, 1971 (Box 432)
  - No Mine Workings, No. 31 Filling Station, Ground Plan, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Amonate, Virginia, 1941/04/10 (Box 432)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., eckman Nos. 11 and 12 Mine, Water System, No Mine Workings, 1971/02/11 (Box 432)
  - No Mine Workings, Plan Showing Pocahontas Cemetery, 1978/08/16 (Box 432)
  - No Mine Workings, Map of pipeline location, Virginia/West Virginia border (Box 432)
  - No Mine Workings, Borehole location map along Milan, Comer, and Sagar Camp Branches of Barkers Creek (Box 432)
  - No Mine Workings, Map of .27 Acres of Land at Abbs Valley, Mercer County, West Virginia, 1923/02/08 (Box 433)
  - Nos. 3, 6, 9, and 11 Seams and Powhatan Lease, shows Elkhorn Creek, No Mine Workings, 1947/07/01 (Box 433)
  - Bandy #2, Road Projections (Box 433)
  - Kepler - main belt and track entry, no mine map (Box 433)
  - Timbering Plan, Crane Creek Nos. 11 B-1 and B-2 (Box 433)
  - No Mine Workings, Standard Oil Co., Proposed Lot Sketch, Pocahontas, Virginia (Box 433)
  - High Splint Seam, Wise Co., Virginia and KY; shows almost a dozen coal companies and properties, 1930/11 (Box 434)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Eckman-Page Mine, Water System,No Mine Workings, 1971/02/11 (Box 434)
  - Harlin Co., Kentucky Stratigraphy (Box 434)
  - No Mine Workings, G&A Coal Co., No. 2 Mine (Box 434)
  - Peerless Coal and Coke Co., no mine workings; plans of buildings, parking lots, area around mine on surface; charts (Box 435)
  - Elk Ridge and Powhatan leaseholds, Outcrops of No. 3 Pocahontas Seam and No. 6 Pocahontas Seam, no mine workings, 1949/07/01 (Box 436)
  - No mine workings, No. 5 Seam, Borehole locations, 1963/06 (Box 436)